

5104 Proper Tunghaan Minglanilla, Cebu 6046 ADDRESS

(+63) 943 221 9155 PHONE

johnlloydmayol@gmail.com E-MAIL

https://github.com/mayol27

www.linkedin.com/in/johnlloyd-mayol LINKEDIN

https://mayol27.github.io ONLINE RESUME

ABOUT ME

A skilled IT affluent young professional with more than 1 experience years of in Software Development & Design, Hardware and Software Maintenance and Repair, and Graphics Design enhancing PHP with in Programming Languages (Laravel, Codelgniter, WordPress, CSS, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, GIT, and Yarn).

SKILLS

WORK

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

LARAVEL

CODEIGNITER

PHP

WordPress

JOHN LLOYD SEGISMAR MAYOL

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

EXPERIENCE

(November 2019 – Present)

HiPE Inc.

Software Developer

- + WordPress
- + Laravel, Sass, CSS, HTML, GIT, and Yarn
- + Maintaining Website

(October 2019)

Devcash

THESIS

A SOFTWARE-AS-A-SERVICE FOR CASHIERING SYSTEM FOR MICRO AND SMALL ENTERPRISES

Position: Hipster

Language: Angular.js, PHP, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, Android, and Firebase

(October 2018 - May 2019)

KREDO IT ABROD INC.

ON-THE JOB TRAINING

- + Hardware/Software Technical Support
- + Created Inventory System for the company

(May 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU - MAIN CAMPUS

WORKING SCHOLAR

- + Hardware/Software Technical Support
- + Assisting students and teachers on computer laboratory
- + Sorting and filing documents

EDUCATION

(June 2015 - October 2019)

University of Cebu – Main Campus

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

(June 2011 – March 2015)

Immaculate Heart of Mary Academy – Minglanilla HIGH SCHOOL

ORGANIZATION

(March 2017 - Present)

GDG Cebu - Google Developers Group

(April 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU – ASSOCIATION OF WORKING SCHOLARS (AWS)

(June 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU - PHILIPPINE SOCIETY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STUDENT (PSITS)

MYSQL

BOOTSTRAP

CSS

 HTML

GIT

YARN

TROUBLESHOOT

PERSONALITY

COMMUNICATION

ORGANIZATION

TEAM PLAYER

CREATIVITY

SOCIAL

CERTIFICATES

(2018)

Building Entrepreneurial Ecosystem to Enhance Higher Education Value-Added for Better Graduate Employability (BEEHIVE) – MOOC

(2017)

5th UC-ICT Congress "Sharpening Junior Mobile Technologists"

(2016)

4th UC-ICT Congress "Shaping up Creative Minds through Great UX Design"

REFERENCE

Ms. Ma. Catherine Carumba

Secretary – College of Computer Studies

Contact: 255 – 7777 loc. 113

Ms. Lina J. Perez

UCEMPC – Secretary Contact: 255 – 7777 loc. 136

Ms. Jerrah Marie Son

Laboratory Supervisor – CCS

Contact: 0923 - 866 - 7880